(WOMAN MOANING)
(BEDSPRINGS SQUEAKING)
(MOANING)
Mm. Oh. yeah. baby.
Oh. yeah.
(PANTS)
I'm gonna take a shower.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(WIND CHIMES RATTLING)
(TWIGS SNAPPING)
(♪♪♪)
(WHIRRING)
(THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND'S "LOOKING
FOR THE MAGIC" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ All my life I'm looking for the magic ♪
♪ I've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a sexy little tragic ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Stay a while till the city is a desert ♪
♪ She's been looking for the treasure ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in my eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in my eyes ♪♪
(♪♪♪)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(♪♪♪)
Huh. Looks like Erik Henson's home.
PAUL: Yeah. I heard he left his
wife for some college student.
He might be living here full time now.
Oh. that's a shame.
We're so isolated up here.
it might be nice to have a neighbor.
I guess.
I got this.
Okay.
That's funny.
What?
It's open.
Doesn't look like
anyone's been in here.
Oh. you know. I bet the workmen left the
door open last time they were here.
I'll get the groceries out of the car
and check on the furnace.
(♪♪♪)
So your parents are pretty waded. right?
Yeah. I guess.
My dad retired from KPG last year. and
he got an insane severance package.
Wait. KPG?
As in. the defense contractor?
Yeah.
He was just in marketing. though.
Why?
Is that a problem for you. babe?
Having dinner with fascists?
No. No. I want to meet your family.
I hope this means there's gonna be
some good booze at your place. though.
(SIGHS)
Probably not.
My mom's on medication.
Can we stop somewhere
and get some. then?
Yes. we should. Good call. Heh.
Yes
(♪♪♪)
(THUDDING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
Hey. I lit the furnace. Sorry.
You okay?
Were you just upstairs?
No. I was in the basement.
Did you hear that. just now?
Hear what?
I heard footsteps.
I think someone's in the house.
Are you sure?
Paul. we gotta get out of here!
Aubrey.
Hurry up!
No. You go outside.
I'm gonna check the upstairs.
You come outside with me!
It's a creaky old house.
Paul! There is someone up there!
(SIGHS)
I'll take this with me. Okay?
Are you happy?
No!
All right. You wait outside.
I'll be out in a minute.
Careful.
I will.
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
Hello?
(FOOTSTEPS)
(THUMPING)
(♪♪♪)
Oh!
Crispian!
Dad.
You scared the shit out of me!
Yeah.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Oh. God.
Not to get off
on the wrong foot here.
but why is Mom
in the driveway crying?
Oh. God. Come with me.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS DESCENDING STAIRS)
(♪♪♪)
Hey.
(AUBREY SOBBING)
You Okay?
Crispian and I looked in every room on
the second floor. There's nobody there.
AUBREY: Oh. God.
I'm so silly.
(SNIFFLES)
Honey. I'm sorry.
No. No.
You're embarrassed.
PAUL: No. I'm not.
You must be Erin.
ERIN: Yes.
Nice to meet you.
ERIN: Nice to meet you.
Glad you could make it.
Yeah. thanks for having me.
Hey. you. Come here.
It's okay.
Oh. we brought whiskey.
Well. come on in.
We'll be there in a minute.
Heh. What's going on?
I... I... Don't ask. I don't know.
So your dad bought this place
to fix up?
Yeah. Supposed to be
his retirement project.
something for him to work on.
but I'm pretty sure so far
he's just paid other people
to work on it.
Hey!
(BEDSPRINGS SQUEAK)
You're gonna break this bed.
It's like a hundred years old.
Sorry. Your folks seem cool.
I mean. for people with money.
You're lucky.
(SCOFFS)
I guess.
No. you are.
You don't know what most people would
give to have folks like yours.
(CRISPIAN SIGHS)
Whatever that means.
(CHUCKLES)
Come here.
So your brothers and sister
get in tomorrow?
Yeah. Tomorrow is my parents'
actual anniversary.
Thirty-five years.
can you imagine?
No. I can't. really.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Well. I look forward to meeting
the rest of your family tomorrow.
They're something.
It's been a long time
since we've all been together
so it should be interesting.
How so?
You'll see.
(♪♪♪)
(CREAKING)
(MAN 1 SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON TV)
(MAN 2 SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
MAN 2: Not in person?
WOMAN: It's crazy.
ERIN: Not in person.
MAN 2: Like old black and white videos.
ERIN: You've seen them.
You've seen the videos.
But when they stand up. they're taller
than you. and if they've got baby...
I feel like kangaroos fight guys
named Gentleman Jack.
It's serious.
Like. twisty. curly.
Hey.
How you doing?
Morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
Hey. buddy.
You ever see kangaroos fight?
Stop!
KELLY: Okay. okay.
Kelly?
Do some funny little...
Up on their tails?
KELLY: Okay.
Ow! Don't hit me.
Stop it. Come on.
Pussy.
Don't.
You almost hit my face.
KELLY: Crispian...
DRAKE: Don't kiss him. Don't
kiss my wife. It's rude.
Ugh. Gross! That is sick.
Thank you.
Come here and kiss me.
KELLY: Oh. I'm sorry. He's your brother.
DRAKE: Yeah.
KELLY: I'm not allowed
to kiss your brother.
Reminds me of when you were a kid.
You should've seen him.
No. you shouldn't have.
Oh. yeah?
Yeah. He was like a little chubby angel.
Really?
KELLY: A little cherub.
DRAKE: Yeah.
I was always a little chubby.
He says "only a little chubby."
CRISPIAN: I have a round face.
That doesn't mean I'm fat.
It doesn't mean he's fat.
ERIN: It means you're beautiful.
DRAKE: All the fat on him means he's fat.
Don't go just by his face.
CRISPIAN: I'm not fat.
(PAPER RUSTLING)
Hey.
Oh. hello.
Um. I was just wondering if you need
any help in here with anything.
I think I'm all set.
Okay.
Actually... Erin?
Yeah?
I am out of milk.
Oh. Uh. okay.
Could you go over
to the neighbor's house
and see if he has some?
His name's Erik.
Okay.
Well. I'll be right back.
PAUL: How's this look. Drake?
DRAKE: Beautiful. Great color.
PAUL: Grain looks nice. doesn't it?
DRAKE: Yeah.
CRISPIAN: I don't know about this grain.
What's going on over here?
Work.
Hey. babe.
ERIN: Boys. You look so adorable.
Can you hold that?
Ready?
Beautiful.
Come join us. Erin.
Your mom just asked me
to go to your neighbor's
to see if I could borrow some milk.
Really?
ERIN: Yeah.
CRISPIAN: All right.
I'll be back in a minute.
PAUL: Sounds like your mom.
DRAKE: That's right.
Don't start.
Don't start with me.
I'm gonna go check on Kelly.
Looks so good. Dad.
PAUL: Thanks. Drake.
So how'd that fellowship thing
turn out?
Oh. Uh...
Not so good.
No?
No. Uh...
I guess there were a lot of applicants
this year. and...
I haven't exactly been
published recently. so...
Well. there are some people
that aren't published
that do get the fellowship.
you know.
Shut the door.
Where'd your brother
find that girl?
I don't know. Student?
Former student?
Huh.
Current student.
(SCOFFS)
I'll bet she's kind of annoying.
Accent's just. like.
so jarring to me.
(THUDDING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
Hey. I lit the furnace. Sorry.
You okay?
Were you just upstairs?
No. I was in the basement.
Did you hear that. just now?
Hear what?
I heard footsteps.
I think someone's in the house.
Are you sure?
Paul. we gotta get out of here!
Aubrey.
Hurry up!
No. You go outside.
I'm gonna check the upstairs.
You come outside with me!
It's a creaky old house.
Paul! There is someone up there!
(SIGHS)
Babe. don't.
Okay. I don't...
I'm not feeling this right now. okay?
Don't give me that look.
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
Do you have any Vicodin?
Yeah. It's in my purse.
(♪♪♪)
(THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND'S "LOOKING FOR
THE MAGIC" PLAYING FAINTLY OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
(CLEARS THROAT)
(WHIRRING)
(THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND'S "LOOKING
FOR THE MAGIC" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
ERIN: Hello? Is anyone home?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
♪ All my life I'm looking for the magic ♪
♪ I've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a sexy little tragic ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪♪
(ENGINE STOPS)
Aimee!
Hi. Mommy!
Oh. honey.
Look at you! You are so beautiful.
AIMEE: Thank you. I lost a little weight.
AUBREY: You look great.
AIMEE: Thank you.
AUBREY: You must be Tariq.
Yes. Nice to meet you.
AUBREY: Nice to meet you.
My little Felix.
Hi. Mom.
I'd like you to meet Zee.
my girlfriend.
AUBREY: Zee?
With two E's. Z-E-E.
Wow. That's unique.
Nice to meet you. Zee.
Come on inside. everyone.
Come in.
AIMEE: Where's Crispian?
Did he bring his new girlfriend?
(LAUGHS THEN SQUEALS)
This is my boyfriend.
TARIQ: Hi.
Crispian.
How you doing?
You must be Erin.
ERIN: Yes.
Oh. my gosh. You're so beautiful.
ERIN: Oh-ho-ho.
Thank you!
Hey. Good to see you.
You're Erin?
Yeah. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. Heard a lot about you.
Oh. And. Zee. right?
Erin.
I know.
PAUL: Hey. where's my princess?
AIMEE: Daddy!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
This is my boyfriend. Tariq.
How are you? Welcome.
Nice to meet you. Thank you.
Who'd like a glass of wine?
I would.
I'll take some wine.
Let me take care of that right now. Felix.
Dad.
AUBREY: I just want you all to know
(VOICE BREAKING) how much it means
to us that you're all here. So...
Thank you for coming.
Oh. She's so cute. I'm in love.
Shh.
(UTENSIL CLINKING ON GLASS)
PAUL: Let's bow our heads.
Dear Heavenly Father.
we thank thee for thy food.
Feed our souls on the bread of life.
and help us to do our part.
with kind words
and loving deeds. Amen.
ALL: Amen.
And thanks to Mom and Dad.
For having us ah here together.
PAUL: It's our measure.
(CHATTERING)
Um. so. Tariq. what do you do?
Uh. ahem. I'm a filmmaker.
Is that right?
AIMEE: Yeah. He's really good.
I don't think I know any filmmakers.
That is so...
interesting.
TARIQ: There's not a lot of us.
KELLY: Have you been on TV?
Not on TV.
I've only made one documentary.
it was at the Cleveland Underground
Film Festival. 2008.
What is an underground
film festival?
Do they show the movies
underground?
TARIQ: No. no. They show them
aboveground. but they...
They show intellectual films.
DRAKE: So like an
intellectual film festival?
Do you do commercials?
Because those are my favorite.
AIMEE: No. he doesn't do commercials.
Mm-mm. No.
Really? I just think that is just the
height of the art form these days.
It is just short and punchy.
you really gotta just Zing the ideas
on in there.
That's why I watch TV.
I just think it's so...
it's better than the shows now.
He makes documentaries. so...
it's different.
Yeah. but I think that I've seen
documentary commercials.
I don't think they have to be
limited to any particular thing.
It's not a... You know. I mean. the starving-artist
thing just never made sense to me.
I just think you should consider it. Tariq.
TARIQ: Sure.
ERIN: That's no fair!
CRISPIAN: Give ii back.
That was mine.
ERIN: Stealer.
So. Erin. are you still in school?
Um... Heh.
Yes. I am. I'm in my final year.
I'm finishing my Master's.
That's great. good for you.
KELLY: In what?
ERIN: In literature.
Wow.
So were you a student of Crispian's?
I was. But I'm not anymore.
Not anymore.
Mm-mm.
She was my TA.
but we stopped. because we figured
that that was inappropriate.
(SOFTLY)
It's a little unprofessional.
What?
(IN NORMAL VOICE) What's that?
CRISPIAN: What you just said.
What was that?
About what?
You said it's unprofessional.
Is there something else
you wanted to say to me?
DRAKE: No. I was just agreeing with you.
You weren't agreeing with me.
I mean. I... What he...?
I thought he said it was unprofessional?
Don't look at her. I'm right here.
Crispian.
What?
PAUL: We're having a dinner here.
I'm having a conversation
with my brother.
Is there something that you wanna say.
because I feel like...
I don't know what you want.
I don't think that you're in any position
to be judging my moral decisions.
Who says I'm judging you?
CRISPIAN: You are. with your eyes.
It's a big semantics conversation.
CRISPIAN: The whole time you've been here
you've been needling me.
and I'm not putting up with it.
DRAKE: You are so jealous of me.
I'm jealous of you?
Do we have to do this at the dinner table
right now? Please. I...
(ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
CRISPIAN: I'm jealous of you?
DRAKE: Always been jealous of me.
What have I done?
Who have I been jealous of?
DRAKE: I make more money than you.
(♪♪♪)
(ARGUING CONTINUES)
AUBREY: Every time we have dinner.
you have to argue like this?
Pam. can you get a handle
on these boys?
(♪♪♪)
PAUL: Crispian. your mother's upset.
What the fuck is that?
DRAKE: Look in the mirror!
CRISPIAN: You look like The Elephant Man.
(ARGUING CONTINUES)
CRISPIAN: What can you not?
What can you not believe?
Go ahead and tell me what
you can possibly not believe.
What could come out of your mouth that's interesting
or of merit or value? I mean. I've had enough.
(TARIQ CHOKING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Ow! Aah!
AIMEE: Oh. my God!
(SCREAMING)
Oh. my God! Aah!
Help me. Crispian!
Help me get her up.
We have to get out of here!
Aimee. no!
DRAKE: Mom. get down! Get
away from the window!
(GROANS)
Aah!
PAUL: Drake!
(DRAKE SCREAMING)
CRISPIAN: Is he all right?
AUBREY: Oh. my God!
(DRAKE SCREAMING)
PAUL: Aubrey. get down!
ERIN: Get down. get down. get down!
PAUL: Stay down. stay down!
ERIN: Get down. get down!
Stay away from the windows.
Get down!
Crispian! Get Drake. get over here.
Drake! Stay down!
KELLY: Someone fucking do something!
Hey. hey. hey. It's okay. It's okay.
Look at me. You're gonna be fine. okay?
Just stay down. Okay. We gotta call 911.
We're all gonna die!
I don't have a signal.
I don't have one. either.
ERIN: Does anybody have a signal?
I had a signal today.
I was able to use the phone today!
Dad! Dad. they must be using a jammer.
What?
A cell-phone blocker.
They're illegal. but you can get them
on the Internet for 30 bucks.
Felix. you fucking low-life!
What are you calling me a low-life for?
I'm just trying to hem.
DRAKE: That's no fucking surprise
you're into that sketchy shit!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oh. my God! We're gonna fucking die!
Oh. my God!
ERIN: Crispian. grab your brother.
carry him out of this room!
Go. go. go! Go. go. go!
Okay. You're gonna grab this chair.
Get yourself out of here!
Cover your face and run!
Stay low! Go!
Aimee. go!
Grab the chair! Go!
(SCREAMING)
Aubrey? Aubrey?
Aubrey. Aubrey.
No. I can't! No!
PAUL: I'm here with you. It's gonna
be okay. Come on. Let's go! Ready?
ERIN: Go. go. go!
Come on.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
We have to pull this out. right?
DRAKE: Yes.
Somebody pull it out! Pull xl out!
AUBREY: Maybe we should...
No. no. no. no.
No clipping. no pulling.
Can you just gently place your hands
over the wound slightly? That's it.
(DRAKE SCREAMING)
ERIN: Breathe!
DRAKE: No. no. no. no. Don't do it.
No. Stop!
KELLY: I'm sorry.
Drugs. babe! Find me drugs!
My purse. Someone hand me my purse.
DRAKE: Stop moving! Aw. fuck!
ERIN: Keep your hands on it. please!
DRAKE: No. don't! Oh!
Stop!
(♪♪♪)
Oh. my God.
What is happening to us?
What the hell is going on?
I have no fucking idea.
FELIX: Dad. do you see anyone?
I don't. Do you see anyone?
No.
Somebody should make a run
for the cars.
And try to go get help!
AUBREY: No! We can't go out there.
It's the only way.
It's the only way we're out of this.
Whoever's the fastest runner.
Who is that?
I'm the fastest. but I've got this
fucking arrow in my back.
CRISPIAN: What does your shoulder have
to do with your legs? I'm the fastest.
He has a fucking arrow in his back!
Stop yelling at me. Kelly!
How the fuck do you know it has to do with
your legs if you never run. you fat fuck?
I'm not fat anymore! Damn it!
Shut the fuck up!
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
I'm the fastest! You guys never
give me any credit for anything!
Look. it's not about that.
Nobody needs to run.
We need to all stay inside.
You don't believe in me!
Honey. we believe in you.
We believe in you.
I can run three miles in 23 minutes.
I'm gonna do it.
Aimee. no! No!
FELIX: Aimee. you can do this.
I believe in you. okay?
Just get out where you can make
a phone call to get help.
Zee. help me move this.
Help me get this out of the way.
PAUL: Felix!
(♪♪♪)
I can do this. Daddy.
Get down!
We'll pull the doors open
at the last second.
They're not gonna be expecting her
to be coming out full speed.
(WHIMPERING)
(NECK CRACKING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
PAUL: Help us! Help me!
Get her inside! Help me! Baby!
What happened? What happened?
(SCREAMING)
PAUL: Aimee!
(♪♪♪)
(AUBREY & KELLY
SCREAMING AND SOBBING)
(CHOKING)
AUBREY: Oh. my God. My baby!
Oh. God. Oh. God. Oh. no!
Oh. my God!
Oh. no. My God.
(AUBREY & KELLY
SCREAMING AND SOBBING)
CRISPIAN: Erin!
What are you doing?
(LOCKS CLICKING)
We need to make sure all the doors
and the windows are locked.
What?
(♪♪♪)
(SIGHS)
(WINDOW CLOSES)
(LOCK CLICKS)
Babe. Hey. What are you doing?
Some places. if you text 911.
they get it as a voice-mail.
If you even have one bar
you can send a text. Come on!
Those things are useless.
I'll have to keep trying.
(AUBREY SOBBING)
Okay. the second floor is clear.
Should be safer than down here.
PAUL: Aubrey. come on.
Come on. Come on.
AUBREY: No.
Oh. my God. no.
I'm taking her upstairs.
ERIN: That's a good idea.
Drake. we need to take care
of this shoulder.
It's fine. I can't feel it anymore.
Are you sure?
Don't touch it. Don't touch it.
Okay. we're all gonna
get out of this.
We need to cover up
and lock all the windows.
I've never seen you act like this before.
Well. it's a unique situation.
We still need someone to go
and try to get some help.
We should stay in and look everything.
and wait till the police come.
In fact. we should hang a sign out
an upstairs window. SOS or something.
That's a good idea.
I can pull a sheet off the bed upstairs.
(AUBREY WHIMPERING)
PAUL: We're almost there. Come on.
Stay with me.
I have to go check on the kids.
(WHIMPERING)
(SNIFFLING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SOBBING)
(♪♪♪)
(AUBREY GASPS)
(AUBREY SCREAMS)
(THUD)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
DRAKE: Get out of the way! Move!
CRISPIAN: Oh. my God.
Mom.
(♪♪♪)
Oh. no. No! No! No! Oh. God! No!
No! Aubrey! No!
Oh. no! No!
(SOBBING)
I have to go see her.
I have to go see her!
DRAKE: Dad. Dad. No. Stay down here.
Stay down here with us.
(SOBBING)
Why would anybody do this?
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(SCREAMING)
KELLY: Oh. my God!
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Kelly!
No. Drake!
Drake!
DRAKE: Kelly!
(SCREAMS)
Fuck!
(GROANING)
What happened?
(KELLY SCREAMING)
Help! Somebody help me!
Somebody help! Help me!
Can you grab a rag?
FELIX: Yeah. okay.
Maybe we should try to run.
I mean. Kelly made it.
At least get to a car or something.
I'll try. I'll try. You guys stay here.
No. no. no. Wait. I'll come with you.
Zee. hold this.
But we'd have to carry Drake.
And Dad...
He... He can't run right now.
I'll go get the car.
I'll bring it right up to the front door.
Then you and Felix and Zee
carry Drake and Dad out.
Make sense?
Babe. it'll be okay.
I can do this.
It'll be just a second.
Honey?
Take this.
(SOBBING)
(THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND'S "LOOKING
FOR THE MAGIC" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
Hello? Sir? Sir? Let me in!
Let me in!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Open the fucking door!
Unlock the door! Let me in! Hello! Hello!
(WHIMPERING)
♪ Stay a while till the city is a desert ♪
(PANTING)
♪ She's been looking for the treasure ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
(SOBBING)
I Baby. in my eyes
Baby. in my eyes ♪
(SHRIEKS)
♪ Is like an hourglass sometime ♪♪
(♪♪♪)
(KELLY COUGHING)
(KELLY SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(WHIRRING)
(DWIGHT TWILLEY'S "LOOKING FOR THE
MAGIC" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ All my life I'm looking for the magic ♪
♪ I've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a se... ♪♪
I think it's safe to assume
the other cars are out. but...
(PANTING)
I didn't see anybody out there.
Maybe Kelly...
Maybe she got past them.
I mean. it gives us a chance.
What do you mean?
I'm going back out there.
No. you're not.
CRISPIAN: Yeah.
Yeah. I mean. I didn't see anyone.
Maybe it's over.
Wait. so what. you're just gonna leave
the rest of us here?
Clearly. we need some help. man.
We need to get somebody out there.
in here.
I'm gonna go to the neighbor's.
As soon as I'm a safe distance away.
I'll try to text and call.
You guys stay in here.
Keep each other safe.
I'll come back. I'll come right back.
ERIN: Wait. Crispian.
Don't go. I'm serious.
Everything's gonna be fine
out there.
You just stay in here.
Take care of yourself.
I'll come back soon. okay? Okay?
You promise?
I promise.
See you soon.
(LOCK CLICKS)
I think it's safe to say
at least one of them is already inside.
You think the person who killed my wife
is still in this house?
I'd assume so. yeah.
How is he. Zee?
Looks like the bleeding stopped.
Let's get him in there.
hide him someplace safe.
Felix. can you give us a hand?
On three. One. two. three.
(GRUNTING)
What's the best room
for us all to be in?
All the rooms have windows
in them. except for the basement.
No. the basement's a bad idea.
They could just pour gas down the
stairs and throw in a match.
We should stay in there and keep boarding
up the windows. Shit. speaking of.
(♪♪♪)
Okay. we should each carry a weapon.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
So your dad bought this place
to fix up?
Yeah. Supposed to be
his retirement project.
something for him to work on.
but I'm pretty sure so far
he's just paid other people
to work on it.
Hey!
(BEDSPRINGS SQUEAK)
You're gonna break this bed.
It's like a hundred years old.
Sorry. Your folks seem cool.
I mean. for people with money.
You're lucky.
(SCOFFS)
I guess.
No. you are.
You don't know what most people would
give to have folks like yours.
(CRISPIAN SIGHS)
Whatever that means.
(CHUCKLES)
Come here.
So your brothers and sister
get in tomorrow?
Yeah. Tomorrow is my parents'
actual anniversary.
Thirty-five years.
can you imagine?
No. I can't. really.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
ERIN: Anyone know this guy?
Although it's kind of hard to tell.
(♪♪♪)
Hey. I'm sure Crispian's fine.
Crispian's a tough guy.
No. he's not. but thanks.
Thanks for the help. by the way.
Hey. you...
You seemed to have a handle on it.
Yeah. don't worry about it.
(PANTING)
Hey. where's your dad?
Where's the circuit box?
I don't know.
I think it's in the basement.
Why don't you go look for it? I'm gonna
go upstairs and try to find my clad.
Oh!
Dad!
Felix!
(WHISPERING) One of
them was in the bedroom.
They've been watching us for days.
While we were sleeping.
This wasn't a random attack. Felix.
Dad. it's okay.
Yeah.
Calm down.
You understand what I'm saying?
Our family is being targeted.
(♪♪♪)
(GASPING)
(CHOKING)
(GURGLING)
Really? You had to do that
right in front of me?
Are you saying something?
Yeah. you know what? Never mind.
You Okay?
Yeah. I just...
I just need to get washed up.
(♪♪♪)
(WATER RUNNING)
(FAUCET HANDLE CREAKS)
(♪♪♪)
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(PLATES AND GLASSES SHATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(PANTING)
(♪♪♪)
(GASPS)
(YELLING)
(SCREAMS)
Hey.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(MAN SCREAMS THEN GROANING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(♪♪♪)
I woke up in there.
Yeah. You blacked out.
We put you there to hide you.
Thanks.
Welcome.
(GROANS)
Where's Kelly?
Uh...
I don't know.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Are you guys okay?
What's going on?
We heard noises.
so we stayed upstairs.
What happened?
One of them came in
and attacked us.
I stabbed him and he ran away.
Come on.
FELIX: You stabbed him?
ERIN: Yeah.
FELIX: Do you think you
might have killed him?
No. he ran out the door.
Was there anyone upstairs?
We didn't find anyone.
Whoever was there
could have climbed out the window.
Is your dad okay?
Yeah. He...
He just needed to lie down.
How many of them
do you think there are?
There'd have to be
at least two more of them.
Well. maybe they're gone.
Maybe you scared them off.
(GROANING)
Come here.
Let's not count on that. Come on.
There's some tools left in the basement
that I think we could use.
Let's head down there.
Okay. Grab anything sharp or heavy
that might make a good weapon
but you need to do it fast.
We've gotta be upstairs.
FELIX: Yeah. let's go through Dad's tools.
There's plenty of stuff
we could use there.
Zee. can you grab these?
Okay. That'll be enough
to get started.
Let's go. And don't take too long!
(♪♪♪)
ERIN: Drake doesn't need
to see her like this.
Zee. let me show you
something quickly?
(METAL CLATTERING)
Okay. so you just want to make sure
that the nail goes all the way through.
(HAMMERING)
See that?
Mm-hm.
Just do. say. four or five on this one?
And we'll just do as many as we can.
Okay.
Can I ask you something?
(HAMMERING)
How did you learn all this stuff?
Well. I had kind of a Weird childhood.
I grew up on a survivalist compound.
I haven't even told Crispian that yet.
Good answer.
Well. I guess when I was born.
my dad got kind of paranoid.
He was convinced that the world
was gonna run out of resources
in a matter of years.
Found a lot of guys who agreed with
him. and we all moved to the Outback.
Basically. if things got too
overpopulated. even out there.
he wanted me to be able
to take care of myself.
Moved to the States
with Mom when I was 15
but I learned a lot beforehand.
Wow. That's crazy.
Got some things here.
So nobody knows where Crispian is?
No. he... He ran out
right after Kelly did.
All right. I gotta go look for them.
I at least have to try.
I can't leave Kelly out there.
What do you mean?
Drake. Kelly's dead.
What?
FELIX: Kelly's dead.
You didn't know that?
Oh. God. I'm sorry.
I didn't want to have to tell you
like this. but she got killed.
Her body's up there
on the floor right now.
Drake. I'm sorry. I...
Shut up! Felix!
I know you cared about her.
Shut up! Shut up! Stop talking!
(SLICING)
I'm sorry.
(FLESH SQUELCHING)
(GRUNTS THEN GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Would you just die already?
This is hard enough for me.
Mm-hm.
Finished that one?
Cool. You know. it might not be a
bad idea to do at least one more.
I'm gonna go check
on their dad upstairs.
When the boys come up.
make sure they have some rope.
Uh. I can do it. I can go.
Do you wanna come with me?
We can go together.
No. that's okay.
I'll just do another board.
Okay. Be careful.
(♪♪♪)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(♪♪♪)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(♪♪♪)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(♪♪♪)
(YELLING)
MAN: Oh! Oh. fuck!
Oh! Oh. you motherfucker!
Oh. fuck!
FELIX: Hey. Would you
mind checking on that?
I believe this is
what I'm paying you for.
(♪♪♪)
Uh. thanks.
(SIGHS)
What a fucking disaster.
It's okay. baby. It'll be over soon.
(BOTH MOANING)
I'm not really in the mood
right new. Zee.
Come on. I'll make it quick.
I want you to fuck me on this bed.
next to your dead mom.
What? Why would you even
say something like that?
(SIGHS)
You never want to do
anything interesting.
I don't think that's a fair criticism.
Fuck me next to
your dead mom. then.
This conversation is over.
(♪♪♪)
Hm.
MAN: Oh! Fuck. Unh!
(GROANING)
Whoa. whoa. wait! Don't do that!
You don't want your DNA
in here. man.
I'll clean it up later.
Just like the rest
of this fucking mess.
Excuse me?
You say that like it's my fault.
Listen. Just so we're perfectly clear.
I just had to kill my own brother
because you guys keep
getting beat up by some girl!
I had to stab my brother.
more than once!
You were supposed to do that.
For all the good you guys did in here.
you could have stayed outside
with your fucking crossbows!
You wanna talk about brothers?
That's my brother.
laying dead right there.
And unlike you.
I liked my brother.
Look. I'm sorry. I didn't know that.
I mean.
I knew you guys served together.
I didn't know
you were related. though.
Man. she really fucked him up good.
huh?
(♪♪♪)
I'm just trying to think of reasons
why I shouldn't kill you!
I'll... I'll pay you more.
What's that?
You kill me. you get nothing.
You pull this off. I'll give you 400.000.
Okay? I was supposed
to give you 2. right?
But you should have your brother's share.
That's only fair.
Plus. I'M throw in an extra 100. Each.
If we can finish this. Okay?
That's half a million for you.
And 300.000 for you. I'm looking at. uh...
(FELIX GRUNTING)
I won't... I won't be able to pay you
until my inheritance comes through
but I'll have it soon.
We just need to finish this!
We did make it this far. man.
You two better be getting
enough money to pay us!
Would I be doing this if I wasn't?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
I got it.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(♪♪♪)
(GRUNTS THEN COUGHING)
Get up! Get after her! Get after her!
(GRUNTING)
(CLATTERING)
(♪♪♪)
Hell. the cops could be driving here
right now. for all we know.
What it they come across her down the road?
Did you even think about that?
You need to calm down.
Don't fucking tell me to calm down. Tom.
This entire situation is out of control.
We don't even know
what's going on.
She's hurt.
She's not faster than us.
You stick to the road. You don't
see her. you come back here.
Well. where are you going?
Back to the house
to check on Craig
and to make sure
she's not doubling back.
Wait. give us the crossbow.
Look. you got your machete.
We don't have any weapons.
What are you standing there for?
Give it to me!
(LAUGHS)
You know how to use that thing?
I know how to fucking use it.
I pull the trigger. arrow shoots. right?
Two bolts. Two shots.
You see her. you make it count.
Of course.
(GLASS CRUNCHING)
Shit.
(♪♪♪)
(BULB SHATTERS)
(CLICKING)
(CUCKING CONTINUES)
(GROANING)
(ERIN GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(♪♪♪)
FELIX: What the fuck?
I fucking hit her. didn't I? Get in there.
Give me the crossbow.
Come on!
All right. I'm right behind you.
Okay.
Goddamn it.
(♪♪♪)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Fuck!
It's not even hot.
you dumb bitch. Whoa!
(YELLS)
(ZEE SHRIEKS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(COUGHING)
(YELLING)
(YELLS)
(WHEEZES THEN COUGHS)
(BLENDER WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
(COUGHING)
(ZEE PANTING)
(ZEE SCREAMS)
(♪♪♪)
(SHUDDERING)
(PANTING)
(CELL PHONE PLAYING RINGTONE)
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
MAN: (OVER PHONE)
Felix?
Hey. Felix. is it all done
in there or what?
I saw my signal came back.
Is it over?
Look. I know you're pissed at me
for not helping out.
I just... I couldn't do it. man. I...
I told you this might happen.
(CRISPIAN SIGHS OVER PHONE)
I saw Mom. and the blood.
and you know I'm a pacifist.
I can't... I can't deal
with the violent stuff.
Come on. now. I can hear you breathing
on the other end of the phone.
Felix?
It's... It's fucking freezing out here.
I'm coming inside.
Felix?
(FOOTSTEPS)
Erin.
You're okay.
Where's Felix?
I stuck a blender in his head
and killed him.
Oh.
Okay.
I can't believe you were in on this.
(SIGHS)
Come on. babe. You do know
how broke we are. right?
You would have killed me.
No! That was never
supposed to happen.
Even if you hadn't meant to kill me.
you must have known I could have died.
No.
You were supposed to
be the witness.
A person with a clean record
that could attest that our family
and neighbors had been murdered
by unknown lunatics.
It was. in fact. a very important part
of my plan that you be unharmed.
We needed someone with no motive
to see what had happened here.
(SIGHS)
Someone other than Zee.
obviously.
Where is Zee?
I killed her too.
Oh.
Totally understand.
Listen. I'm sorry
things got so out of control.
but how were we
supposed to know
that you were really good
at killing people?
Which is actually sort of weird.
by the way.
Had you reacted. um. normally.
my parents and siblings
would have been killed.
you'd have been untouched...
and we'd be rich.
We'd be on our way to.
like. a vacation in Paris.
Maybe an engagement?
Okay. Okay.
(SNIFFLES)
There is a silver lining here.
by the way.
I'm now the sole inheritor
of my family's estate.
We're talking millions. babe.
You. Me.
Us.
Look.
Regardless of
our current situation...
or whatever
we're going through right now...
it would be insane
to throw that away.
I mean. look at all
that would be wasted.
I understand it might take a while
to make this up to you.
But in the meantime.
let's think about this logically.
I know you've got
your student loans.
How would $500.000 go towards
fixing that problem?
You could quit your bartending job.
just study full time.
You know you hate that job.
You could have 500.000
within the month.
(SIGHS)
Or I go to jail...
and you get nothing.
(SOFTLY) Hey.
I love you.
I promised you that
I'd come back. didn't I?
Here I am.
(♪♪♪)
(COUGHING AND GASPING)
Why?
Why the fuck not?
(GUNSHOT)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Oh. fuck.
(GASPING)
We need medic and backup
immediately at 5 Edelweiss Drive.
(♪♪♪)
No! Don't!
(GASPS)
(MIND THE GAP'S
"LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC" PLAYING)
♪ All my life I've been
Looking for the magic ♪
♪ I've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a sexy little tragic ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in my eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in my eyes ♪
l' On the tips of Vegas
Sexy little lay. girl ♪
♪ She been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Stay a while till the city is a desert ♪
♪ She's been looking for the treasure ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in my eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in my eyes ♪
I Because a photograph
Is like an hourglass sometime ♪
I And then I never laugh
Because I never have no time ♪
♪ Oh. in her eyes
To keep. oh. oh. oh ♪
♪ The magic in my eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in my eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh. oh ♪
♪ In her eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in her eyes ♪
♪ Baby. in her eyes ♪♪